Guide to the Richard Bonelli Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Sound recordings
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.2, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 20)
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.9, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 21)
    Thy beaming eyes -- Two grenadiers
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.9, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 22)
    Floods of spring -- Blue moon
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.16, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 23)
    Cuban Love song -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive
  - Andre Kostelanetz. W.A.B.CMar.16, 1935, 1 sound disc: 331/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 24)
    Stothart, Herbert, 1885-1949. Cuban love song -- Trad. Eriee canal
  - Andre Kostelanetz. W.A.B.CMar.16, 1935, 1 sound disc: 331/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 25)
    Trad. Eriee canal -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.20, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 26)
    Speaks, Oley, 1876-1948. Sylvia -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Nemico della patria
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.20, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 27)
    Walton, Kenneth, 1904-1986. I am love -- Drummond, William Henry, 1854-1907. Wreck of the "Julie Plante" --
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.25, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 37, Folder 28)
    Hart, Lorenz, 1895-1943. Blue Moon
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.20, 1935, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 29)
    Hart, Lorenz, 1895-1943. Blue Moon -- Invictus
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.30, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 30)
    Sweet song of long ago -- A sailor's life
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar.30, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 31)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Eri tu -- Song of the musketeers
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CApril 3, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 32)
    Banjo song -- Lolita -- Tobacco road
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CApril 3, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 33)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CMar. 13, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 34)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An Sylvia -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CApr. 13, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 35)
    Love was with me yesterday -- Brothers of Romany
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CApr. 29, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 36)
    Paloma -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Serse. Largo
  - Chesterfield Hour. W.A.B.CApr. 20, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 37)
    Deep river -- Run Mary run -- Come to the fair
  - Ford Synmphony Hour. W.A.B.CMay 26, 1935, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 38)
    Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Danse macabre (Song) -- Tally -Ho! -- Through the years
  - Atwater Kent Hour. W.A.B.COct. 5, 1935 [?], 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 39)
    Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Selections
  - General Motors Hour. W.E.A.F.Feb. 2, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 40)
    Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum
  - General Motors Hour. W.E.A.F.Feb. 2, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 41)
    Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Danse macabre (Song) -- Captain Stratton's fancy
  - General Motors Hour. W.E.A.F.Feb. 2, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 42)
    Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen
  - General Motors Hour. W.E.A.F.Feb. 2, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 43)
    Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum
  - General Motors Hour. W.E.A.F.Feb. 2, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 44)
    Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Danse macabre (Song)
  - General Motors Hour. W.E.A.F.Feb. 2, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 45)
    Captain Stratton's Fancy
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 15, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 46)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Act II, scene two.
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 15, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 47)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 48)
    Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 49)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 50)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 51)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 52)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 53)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 54)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 55)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 56)
  - Metropolitan Opera Broadcast. W.J.ZFeb. 29, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 57)
  - W.A.B.CMar. 8, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 58)
    Danny Deever
  - W.A.B.CMar. 8, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 37, Folder 59)
    Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Chanson du toréador
  - General Electric Hour. W.E.A.FMar. 30, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 60)
    Through the years
  - General Electric Hour. W.E.A.FMar. 30, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 61)
    On the road to Mandalay
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.18, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 62)
    Sweet song of long ago
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.18, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 63)
    Irish names
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.18, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 64)
    Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Soirées musicales. Danza
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.18, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 64)
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.22, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 65)
    Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Prologue
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.22, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 66)
    Come to the fair
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.22, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 67)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An Sylvia
  - Chesterfield Program. W.A.B.CApr.22, 1936, 1 sound disc: aluminum; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 68)
    Out of the twilight
  - Ford Summer Hour. W.J.ZAug. 7, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 69)
    Invictus -- Song of the rangers -- Stars in my eyes
  - Ford Summer Hour. W.J.ZAug. 14, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 70)
    Come to the fair -- Hills of old Wyoming
  - Ford Summer Hour. W.J.ZAug. 21, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 71)
    Tommy Lad -- Stout hearted men -- These foolish things
  - Ford Summer Hour. W.J.ZAug. 28, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 72)
    Through the years -- Song of the vagabonds
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.COct.25, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 73)
    Brown October ale -- Hymn
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.COct.25, 1936, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 74)
    Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Soirées musicales. Danza -- Annie Laurie
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.CFeb.2, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 75)
    Opening announcement -- Captain, my captain
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C and Metropolitan OperaFeb.7 and 13, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 76)
    Tommy Lad -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Act I
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C Feb.7, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 77)
    Captain, my captain -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Il balen del suo sorriso
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C Feb.7, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 78)
    O beauty passing by -- Captain, my captain
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C Feb.7, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 79)
    Tommy lad -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Parsifal. Charfreitagszauber
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C Feb.7, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 80)
    Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Chanson du toréador -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Il balen del suo sorriso
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C Feb.7, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 81)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Il balen del suo sorriso -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Chanson du toréador
  - Metropolitan OperaFeb.13, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 82)
    Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Act 1and 2
  - Firestone HourFeb.22, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 83)
    Because -- I cannot sing the old songs -- Old faithful -- Song of the musketeers
  - Firestone HourFeb.22, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 84)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Gambling scene.
  - Vicks Open HouseMar. 21, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 85)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Di Provenza il mar -- Road to Mandalay
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C Mar. 28, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 86)
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Winterstürme wichen dem Wonnemond -- Rosary
  - Ford Symphony Hour. W.A.B.C Mar. 28, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 87)
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Israel in Egypt. Dank sei dir, Herr
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourApr.17, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 88)
    Irish names -- Romberg medley
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourApr.17, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 89)
    Irish names -- Romberg medley -- Stout-hearted men -- London town -- When I grow too old to dream
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourApr.24, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 90)
    Captain Stratton's fancy -- Sweethearts make love -- Through the years
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJune 12, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 91)
    Begin the beguine -- Duet: When you are away -- Border ballad
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJune 20, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 92)
    Introduction and without a song -- Gipsy John
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJuly 4, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 93)
    Luna d' estate -- L' amour toujours l'amour -- Song of the musketeers -- Sweetest story ever told
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourApr. 24, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 94)
    Rangers song
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourMay 15, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 95)
    Moonlight Madonna -- Ride cowboy ride
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourMay 22, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 96)
    Invictus -- Hop-Li, the riksha man
  - Ford Universal Rhythm Hour, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 98)
    Bird songs at eventide -- Duet: We will always be sweethearts
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJune 20, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 99)
    Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Chanson du toréador -- My little buckaroo
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJune 27, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 100)
    Medley
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJuly 11, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 101)
    Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. An Sylvia -- Schumann, Robert, 1810-1856. Romanzen und Balladen, op. 49. Beiden Grenadiere
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJuly 11, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 102)
    Duet: Canadian boat song -- I' ll see you again
  - Ford Universal Rhythm HourJuly 11, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 103)
    Rosemarie -- Time to go -- I' ll take you home again, Kathleen -- Mountains
  - [Ford Universal Rhythm Hour]July 18, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 104)
    Temple bells -- Because -- Dat's why darkies were born
  - Popular songs, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 105)
    Jesu Joy -- Night and day
  - Popular songsAug.2, [1937?], 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 106)
    Colette -- Don Juan serenade -- Song of the open road -- Dancing in the dark
  - Popular songsAug.15, [1937?], 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 107)
    Deep river -- Song of the vagabonds
  - Popular songsAug.15, and 22, [1937?], 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 108)
    Deep within my heart -- Just a wearyin' for you
  - Popular song and Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Selection.Aug. 22, [1937?], 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 109)
    Show boat medley -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Salut, demeure chaste et pure
  - Various songsAug. 30, [1937?], 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 110)
    Bird song at even tide -- Grand match -- Desert song -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Soirées musicales. Danza
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Selection and Interview[1937?], 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 38, Folder 111)
    Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Winterstürme wichen dem Wonnemond -- Interview
  - Vienna city of dreams. W.A.B.CSept.5, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 112)
  - Dialogue with Richard Bonelli. Kraft Music Hall. ISept.30, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 113)
  - Dialogue with Richard Bonelli. Kraft Music Hall. IISept.30, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 114)
  - Ford HourDec.26, 1937, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 38, Folder 115)
    Christmas carol -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Israel in Egypt. Dank sei dir, Herr
  - Ford Hour. W.A.B.CDec.25, 1938, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 116)
    Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Sleigh
  - Ford Hour. W.A.B.CDec.25, 1938, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 117)
    O little town of Bethlehem -- A star was his candle
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Selections IMar.16, 1940, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 118)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Selections II and Templeton ProgramMar.16, 1940, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 119)
    Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Selections II -- Templeton Program. Johnny and two tiny sisters
  - Opera GuildJan. 1941, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 120)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello I
  - Opera GuildJan. 1941, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 121)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello II
  - Musical Americana. W.E.A.FJan.16, 1941, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 122)
    I cannot sing the old songs
  - Coca-Cola HourSpring, 1941, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 123)
    I cannot sing the old songs -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Selection
  - Metropolitan opera broadcast. W.J.ZMar. 6, 1943, 1 broken sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 124)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Selections I
  - Metropolitan opera broadcast. W.J.ZMar. 6, 1943, 1 broken sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 125)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Selections II
  - Metropolitan opera broadcast. W.J.ZMar. 6, 1943, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 126)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Selections III
  - Treasury Hour. W.Q.X.RApr. 11, 1943, 1 broken sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 127)
    Bird of the wilderness -- Tennyson; Golde. Beauty, passing beauty
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore I1943, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 128)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore II1943, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 129)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore III1943, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 130)
  - National music week interviewMay 3, 1945, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 131)
    Recorded in Salt Lake City, Utah
  - Alec Templeton Time (Radio program) Dec.23, 1946, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 132)
    Cowen, Frederic H. (Frederic Hymen), Sir, 1852-1935. Border ballad -- Vaughan Williams, Ralph, 1872-1958. Songs of travel. Roadside fire; Vagabond
  - Ernst Victor Wolff (Radio program) Dec.23, 1946, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 133)
    Ropartz, Joseph Guy Marie, 1864-1955 Berceuse -- Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Mörike-Lieder. Lied vom Winde
  - Alec Templeton Time (Radio program) Dec.25, 1946, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 134)
    Templeton, Alec, 1910-1963. Gifts -- In summertime on Bredon
  - Alec Templeton Time (Radio program) Dec.25, 1946, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 135)
    Jingle bells -- Rachmaninoff, Sergei, 1873-1943. Prelude
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 136)
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Brockes-Passion. Die ihr Gottes Gnad' versäumet; Volate più dei venti.
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 137)
    Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Floridante. Alma mia -- Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Spanisches Liederbuch. Auf dem grünen Balkon; Italienisches Liederbuch. Und willst du deinen Liebsten sterben sehen
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 138)
    Wolf, Hugo, 1860-1903. Mörike-Lieder. Lied vom Winde -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 32. Ich trage meine Minne -- Matiessen, Huhn und der Karpfen
  - Interview for Children's Hour (Radio program)1940, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 39, Folder 139)
    On "Icarus"
  - 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 39, Folder 140)
    Balcony scene
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 141)
    Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Lieder, op. 19. Wie sollten wir geheim sie halten -- Brahms, Johannes, 1833-1897. Gesänge, op. 43. Mainacht
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 142)
    Duparc, Henri, 1848-1933. Vague et la cloche -- Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Pas d'armes du Roi Jean
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 143)
    Duparc, Henri, 1848-1933. Vie antérieure -- Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Berceaux
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 144)
    Fauré, Gabriel, 1845-1924. Fleur jetée -- Vaughan Williams, Ralph, 1872-1958. Songs of travel
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 145)
    Golde, Franne. Beauty, passing beauty -- Vaughan Williams, Ralph, 1872-1958. Songs of travel. Bright is the ring of words; Roadside fire
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 146)
    Horsman, Edward, 1873-1918. Bird of the wilderness -- Templeton, Alec, 1910-1963. Gifts -- Hughes, H. arr. Next market day; Ballynure ballad
  - Town Hall Recital1947, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 147)
    Heley Hutchinson, Victor. Old mother Hubbard -- Hageman, Richard, 1882-1966. Donkey
  - The Hills of HomeNov. 14, 1948, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 148)
    Carnegie Hall. ABC
  - The bells of Saint Mary'sNov. 14, 1948, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 149)
  - Sweet song of long ago; The bells of Saint Mary'sDec. 23, 1948, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 150)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 1, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 151)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 2, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 152)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 3, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 153)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 4, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 154)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 5, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 155)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 6, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 156)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 7, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. Mold problem, removed from box (Box 39, Folder 157)
  - Montemezzi, Italo, 1875-1952. Amore dei tre re. Selections 8, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. Mold problem, removed from box (Box 39, Folder 158)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. Mold problem, removed from box (Box 39, Folder 159)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. Mold problem, removed from box (Box 39, Folder 160)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor. Act I, scene 2 and Act II, scene 1 and 2, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 161)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor. Act II, scene 2, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 162)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor. End of act II, scene 2, and act III, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 163)
  - Midnight in the Madhouse, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 39, Folder 164)
  - Visione Veneziana, 1 sound disc: acetate; 8 in. (Box 39, Folder 165)
  - The golden age of opera, 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 166)
    Side 1: Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Balen del suo sorriso -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern -- Trad. Swing low, swing chariot -- Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Danse macabre (Song) -- Taylor, Deems, 1885-1966. Captain Stratton's fancy.Side 2: Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Fedora. Donna russa -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Roi de Lahore. Promesse de mon avenir -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Serse. Ombra mai fù -- Korngold, Erich Wolfgang, 1897-1957. Tote Stadt. Mein Sehnen, mein Wähnen -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Zazà. Zazà, piccola zingara -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Hérodiade. Vision fugitive -- Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Hamlet. O vin, dissipe la tristesse -- Speaks, Oley, 1876-1948. On the road to Mandalay
  - The golden age of opera (duplicate), 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 167)
  - The golden age of opera (duplicate), 1 sound disc: acetate; 12 in. (Box 39, Folder 168)
  - Rosary, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. Set of discs originally in tin box #1. Original order of discs kept (Box 45, Folder 169)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aida. Selections I. Act I trio. Mar.2, 1940, 1 sound disc: acetate; 10 in. Set of discs originally in tin box #1. Original order of discs kept (Box 45, Folder 170)
    Metropolitan Opera. Bampton, Ruth, 1902-